<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
	<channel>
        <item>
			<id>1</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>Eddie Torres and Shani Talmor</name>
			<loc>New York/USA</loc>
			<desc1>Eddie Torres, also known as “The Mambo King”, is a salsa dance instructor.</desc1>
			<desc2>
                Eddie has been dancing and teaching salsa for over four decades. He has trained thousands of dancers, including some of the most important dancers and instructors of the Big Apple and all over the planet like Delille Thomas (Mambo D), Wilton Beltre (the founder of Santo Rico Dance Company), Adolfo Indacochea, Franklin Diaz, Frankie Martinez and Seaon Brystol. Through his dance school, he has taught thousands of people how to dance salsa in his own distinctive style. He also has a children’s dance program that teaches approximately three hundred students a year.
                
            Shani Talmor
                
                Born and raised in Israel, has traveled worldwide presenting her sensual and sexy salsa style. Trained in a variety of dance styles, including ballet, jazz, hip-hop, samba and Afro-Cuban, Shani is an energetic and explosive dancer. She is world-renowned for her unique, sensuous styling and body movement on and off the dance floor. She has powerful stage presence and a passionate love for teaching.</desc2>
			<img>eddie.jpg</img>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>2</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>ADOLFO INDACOCHEA and TANIA CANNARSA</name>
			<loc>Milan/Italy</loc>
			<desc1>Adolfo Indacochea is an explosive and energetic dancer that is known all around the world for his smooth and unique style.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			His mentor, Eddie Torres discovered his talent immediately. 8 months later, Adolfo became one of the elite dancers of the Eddie Torres Company and rising to be one of the newest stars on the New York Mambo scene. 
			
			Adolfo's talent, creative energy and charisma captivates the audience. Because of that, it is impossible to leave his class without a smile on your face. Two of the most foreknown dancers in the world, Adolfo Indacochea and Tania Cannarsa will perform and teach workshops so don't miss this great opportunity to learn from two of the best dancers in the salsa industry.</desc2>
			<img>adolfo.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>3</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>JUAN MATOS and AMNERIS MARTINEZ</name>
			<loc>Milan/Italy</loc>
			<desc1>From talented social dancer to fabulous entertainer: That's Juan Matos. Together with his gifted dancer partner Amneris Martinez they are one of the most expressive dance couples in the world.</desc1>
			<desc2>			
			Whether it is during a social dance or a dance performance, Juan is considered to be one of the best, hottest and most influential dancers of his generation. He has been a huge inspiration for the majority of the "on2" professionals in the salsa world. Natural talent, pure, smooth, classic, and fast feet: those that know Juan Matos, know that we have to be ready for a lot of surprises! 
			
			View one exclusive interview with Amenris Martinez by Latino Chanel TV!</desc2>
			<img>juan_matos.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>4</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>TERRY and CECILE</name>
			<loc>Paris/France</loc>
			<desc1>Salsa Addicted Festival started with them 6 years ago and since then they are your permanent guests.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			Their shows are always different. Not even they ever know beforehand which will be the style of their next choreography. This year, they told us that we will have to wait for a big surprise. We are waiting for them as always.</desc2>
			<img>terry.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>5</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>MORENASSO and ANAIS MILLON</name>
			<loc>Luanda/Angola</loc>
			<desc1>Morenasso (Angolan) and Anais Millon (Martinique/France) have met in 2009 and since then, the SENSUALONDA was born.</desc1>
			<desc2>
                Sensualonda, "the sensual wave", comes from their way of feeling and living this dance, from the physical and vibrating connection that comes out of it.
                
                Just like a boat floating on the waves, their dance expresses sensuality and technical details in the spirit of osmosis and fusion.
                
                With the occasion of their class, they want to share this experience, on the technical level as well as spreading the connection.</desc2>
			<img>morenasso.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>6</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>MOUAZE KONATE</name>
			<loc>Paris/France</loc>
			<desc1>Mouaze is known as one of the biggest salsa artists in France.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			A very charismatic person, an excellent showman, a great choreographer. His style, his technique and his teaching are unique. In 2004, he went to the study at the University in Puerto Rico where he learned more about salsa. Thereafter he went to New York to work together with Eddie Torres. His performances are of a high quality.
			
			Nowadays, Mouaze is known as the ChaCha King.</desc2>
			<img>mouaze.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>7</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>Mania Latina</name>
			<loc>Bucharest/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>Mania Latina is a Latino dance school, located in Bucharest.</desc1>
            <desc2>In 7 years of activity we are proud to say that we met and taught thousands of students. We participated at Latino national and international events and contests, where we gain a lot of prizes. The great challenge was when we organized our own latino international festival “Romantic Latin Festival”, in June 2012. We received a positive feedback and we are proud to say that it was a successful event. Our classes are complex and students can learn: salsa, bachata, merengue, rueda, zouk and kizomba. In time, Mania Latina became more than just a dance school, it’s a family, the members are learning and having fun in the same time and we call them “maniaci”. Our best students form now a famous group and they are invited to participate at different events. Mania Latina has the doors open to all the latino dance lovers who are willing to learn, have fun and socialize in the same time!</desc2>
			<img>manialatina.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>8</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>GIANNI and ROBERTA</name>
			<loc>Bari/Italy</loc>
			<desc1>..will be joining us from Thursday. 
			
			Instructors and performers of the most important events at the national and international level,</desc1>
			<desc2>their professional background includes different styles of Salsa, Caribbean folklore, Afro-Contemporary and Afro-Yoruba Santeria. Gianni is a pioneer and a promoter of the Puertorican, New York, Pachanga, Latin Funk and Boogaloo style in his city where he has become a popular reference for many instructors and dancers. 
			
			Gianni and Roberta's performances are very much appreciated for their originality, high-level technique, clean movements and musicality. They are also trained in Ballet, Modern and Contemporary Dance, Hip hop, Tap Dance and Flamenco.</desc2>
			<img>gianni.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>9</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>AIRE DANCE COMPANY</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>AIRE was (officially) founded on the 8th of January 2012, uniting under the same flag ten enthusiastic people driven by the same passion.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			Why AIRE Dance Company? Because the art of dance motivates us, music guides our rhythm, and emotions inspire us to bring it to you day after day. 
			
			We seek to share our passion for music and dance with the local and international dance communities through workshops, shows and deejaying.</desc2>
			<img>aire.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>10</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>ANDREA and MARIA</name>
			<loc>Napless/Italy</loc>
			<desc1>Andrea Peluso entered the salsa and quickly fell in love with the sound of "New York style" and "Pachanga".</desc1>
			<desc2>
			He studied with world-class artists such as Adolfo Indacochea, Carla Voconi, Angelo Rito, then taking a short but very intense trip with the aim of continuing his training in greater depth. In 2011, he began his artistic journey in tandem with: Maria Lanno, who is a professional dancer, a mixture of passion, sensuality and elegance. 
			
			She trained with world-class artists such as Christina Rodriguez, Juan Matos, Adolfo Indacochea, Carla Voconi and Angelo Rito. After performing at some Italian congresses, including Salsitaly and Eventopeople, in October 2010, they were placed on the 9th place at the World Championships Caribbean Dances in Liberec. 
			
			In addition to the dance, they are focusing their ideas on clothing also creating a line of unique and vintage bow ties: AM Papillon</desc2>
			<img>andreamaria.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>11</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>STEP IN 2 SALSA</name>
			<loc>Brasov/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>Step in2 Salsa’s primary focus is to provide a fun and refreshing program of learning how to dance Salsa and Bachata.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			Edi and Ali always show their passion for their favourite type of dance, Bachata, every time they have the chance to do so. The feelings and emotion shown while they dance Bachata prove both the strong connection that exists between them and the beauty of this type of dance.
			
			Edi and Ali are truly dedicated to 'dance' and this is regularly proven both by their personal success on stage as a couple as well as from the success and enjoyment attained by their students in class. The combination of joy, ambition and the pursuit of quality in all that they do make them ideal dance instructors as they carefully blend 'fun', 'art' and 'professionalism' to create a truly unique dance school.</desc2>
			<img>edi_ali.jpg</img>
		</item>		
		
		<item>
			<id>12</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>TAMAS and VERONIKA</name>
			<loc>Budapest/Hungary</loc>
			<desc1>They are dancing together since 2007. In the beginning, they started to learn the Caribbean dances (like casino, bachata, reggaeton)</desc1>
			<desc2>and they were members of a performing group, later continued with tango argentino. Students of Maria Glotz for one year, they got interested in kizomba. Since this African culture was not really represented in their country, they tried to go festivals (Lisbon, Warsaw, Belgrade) and learn the culture behind the steps, as much as they could, during these events. Permanently improving more styles (Angola, Passada, Flow) and at the same time giving more colorful picture for the interested people. 
			
			In the meantime they got the possibility of becoming the students of the well-known Angolan professor, Pedro Tomas Petchu. Petchu improved their knowledge personally. Since 2011, they are trying to spread the Kizomba dance and culture in Hungary (www.kizomba.hu), and they are organizing congresses several times a year (www.yeskizomba.hu). 
			
			They were invited to participate and to hold classes during international events like Budapest Kizomba Connection, Belgrade International Kizomba Energy - Festival (BIKE) or Kizomba Italian Festival Event (KIFE).</desc2>
			<img>tamasveronica.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>13</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>SALSA WITH ATTITUDE</name>
			<loc>Timisoara/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>attitude.jpg</img>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>15</id>
			<type>instructor</type>
			<name>SALSA FACTORY</name>
			<loc>Bucharest/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>Our salsa dance school opened from the desire of dancing SALSA! It may be a simple reason, but it's the fundamental reason for which Salsa Factory exists.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			Through our classes we wish to open the door to the special world of Latin dancing to all those that want to discover the hot rhythms of Latin styles (salsa, bachata, rumba, pachanga, zouk, kizomba). 
			
			Furthermore, we guarantee that at the end of the class you'll go home not only full of energy but also with new friends in your Facebook list. What better way to socialize other than dancing? Starting from 2008, Salsa Factory obtained important prizes at international events and they are awarded with multiple champion titles in Romania, maxing out with the entry in the top 10 pairs of the world in 2010, in both salsa and bachata! 
			
			Until today, the performance maintained and we're continuing our hard work so we can represent our school and salsa dancing at the highest level. Salsa Factory instructors have a solid background in the world of dancing. They've learned and consolidated their steps and technique in our school but also outside the school, with the help of world renowned instructors. 
			
			Furthermore, by participating to numerous international congresses in Europe, America or Puerto Rico, they're knowledge in Latin dancing or other similar dances increased. The best attribute that Salsa Factory instructors have is their passion for salsa and the desire to teach their students how to dance salsa from the heart.</desc2>
			<img>factory.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>16</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>GRUPO ALAFIA</name>
			<loc>Parma/Italy</loc>
			<desc1>"Grupo Alafia" was born in the summer of 2008 as an idea of Francesco Scalvenzi and Marcello Magnani.</desc1>
			<desc2>
                The group's first goal has always been creating something extremely original and alternative for the salsa audience, taking inspiration by Francesco's creativity and music knowledge. The summer of 2010 was a turning point for the Italian guys: the "Mi Pachanga" show received international recognition by a standing ovation at the New York Salsa Congress, the night of September 5th 2010.
                
                Since then, Grupo Alfia has been invited to participate at most renowned congresses in Europe and all around the world.
                The team has achieved extraordinary success, also for its funny and really effective teaching technique. And finally here they are!
                
                El Grupo returns to Timisoara and they will be teaching and performing at SAF 6!
                
                Ladies get ready!...the "Italian guys" are waiting for you to dance all night long!!...</desc2>
			<img>alafia.jpg</img>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>17</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Saoco</name>
			<loc>Ljubljana/Slovenia</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>saoco.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>18</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>MELODIA PROJECT</name>
			<loc>Bucharest/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>melodia.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>19</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Teddy and Mitko</name>
			<loc>Sofia/Bulgaria</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>teddymitko.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>20</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>BAILARTE</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>bailarte.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>21</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Salsa Picate</name>
			<loc>Brasov/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>picante.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>22</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Streetsalseros</name>
			<loc>Sofia/Bulgaria</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>street.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>23</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>SALSA CALIENTE</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>Salsa Caliente first took the scene in the Spring of 2003 during a dance show organized by the Student's Culture House of Cluj-Napoca.</desc1>
			<desc2>
			In the years that followed, Salsa Caliente had numerous appearances in dance shows, festivities and other events, TV shows, Salsa festivals and congresses, both at home and abroad such as Cluj, Oradea, Targu-Mures, Zalau, Timisoara, Brasov, Bucharest , Iasi, Constanta, Vama Veche, Bulgaria, France, Germany, Cyprus. 
			
			In December 2006, Lucian Ambrosie launched the "Rueda Competition" which has now reached its 8th edition, and in 2010 it became a national competition managing to capture its audience's attention every single time, and not only that, but to also fill the room in the Students' House of Culture of Cluj-Napoca, where the contest has taken place each year. 
			
			Over the years, more than 2,000 students have crossed the threshold of the dance school and the Salsa Caliente dance formation has developed and perfected itself more and more over time. Maintaining their already established style, Salsa Caliente has reached a formula which represents it at its best and which allows a better approach of choreographies as well as an increasing evolution.</desc2>
			<img>caliente.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>24</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Salsoteca</name>
			<loc>Ljubljana/Slovenia</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>salsoteca.jpg</img>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>25</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ WILLY</name>
			<loc>Paris/France</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>willy.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>26</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ MAURI</name>
			<loc>Amsterdam/Netherlands</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>mauri.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>27</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ WILLY</name>
			<loc>Amsterdam/Netherlands</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>willyams.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>28</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ ROMY</name>
			<loc>Bucharest/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>romy.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>29</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ Stilo</name>
			<loc>Budapest/Hungary</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>stillo.jpg</img>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>30</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ SYL</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>syl.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>31</id>
			<type>dj</type>
			<name>DJ MARTIN</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>martin.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>32</id>
			<type>mc</type>
			<name>JUAN MATOS</name>
			<loc>Milan/Italy</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>matos.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>33</id>
			<type>mc</type>
			<name>Romy</name>
			<loc>Bucharest/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>romy2.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>34</id>
			<type>photo</type>
			<name>KHALID JALLI</name>
			<loc>Bruxelles/Belgium</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>khalid.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>35</id>
			<type>photo</type>
			<name>CRISTIAN MITRAN</name>
			<loc>Bruxelles/Belgium</loc>
			<desc1>http://www.cristianmitran.com</desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>mitran.jpg</img>
		</item>

		<item>
			<id>36</id>
			<type>photo</type>
			<name>OVIDIU CIBA</name>
			<loc>Timisoara/Romania</loc>
			<desc1>http://www.ovidiuciba.ro</desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>ciba.jpg</img>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<id>37</id>
			<type>photo</type>
			<name>BOGDAN BUCEVSCHI</name>
			<loc>Cluj Napoca/Romania</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>bogdan2.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>38</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>Eddie Torres</name>
			<link>1</link>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>39</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>Shani Talmor</name>
			<link>1</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>40</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>ADOLFO INDACOCHEA</name>
			<link>2</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>41</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>TANIA CANNARSA</name>
			<link>2</link>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>42</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>Juan Matos</name>
			<link>3</link>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>43</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>Amneris Martinez</name>
			<link>3</link>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>44</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>TERRY TAULIAUT</name>
			<link>4</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>45</id>
			<type>solo</type>
			<name>Cecile Ovide</name>
			<link>4</link>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>46</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Fuego DC</name>
			<loc>Budapest/Hungary</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>fuego.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>47</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>ImprOn2</name>
			<loc>Budapest/Hungary</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>impron2.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>48</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Fernando and Michela</name>
			<loc>Roma/Italy</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>ferna.jpg</img>
		</item>
        <item>
			<id>49</id>
			<type>performer</type>
			<name>Kizomba production</name>
			<loc>Lublijana/Slovenia</loc>
			<desc1></desc1>
			<desc2></desc2>
			<img>kizombaProd.jpg</img>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
